welcome to the stola the stoah is a
digital campfire where we go here and
dialogue about what matters most at the
night's edge what's happening now
[Music]
be brave right be hopeful right despair
is useless you know B have a bias
towards action don't sit on your
ass if you see something to be done do
it reach out to other people you know
events like this are huge remember the
poor people who are who are locked down
by themselves which has got to be a
horrible thing reach out to them I'm you
know daily calling old friends far back
as high school just cuz I'm a natural
extrovert and I love the chat so
I have some extra time and energy so I'm
literally gonna call a friend who I
haven't seen since junior high school
I'll call later today we're going to
chat so don't despair there was hope and
future on the other side of this
hysteresis works in our favor
be ready to join the cadre recruit
others to the cadre this is probably not
quite yet the revolutionary moment but
it may be relatively soon beautiful
beautiful